<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Wifi Saftey Check</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Wifi Saftey Check</string>
    <string name="main_button_start">Start Scan!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_summary">Scan Summary</string>
	<string name="title_activity_explanation">Further Explanation</string>
	<string name="dialog_activate_wifi">Before proceeding, we need you to connect to the network you wish to check.
	    Would you like to connect now?</string>
    
    <!-- Lables -->
    <string name="lable_security">Security:</string>
    <string name="lable_open_wifi">Open Wifi</string>
    <string name="lable_wep">WEP</string>
    <string name="lable_wps">WPS</string>
    <string name="lable_wpa">WPA</string>
    <string name="lable_wpa2">WPA2</string>
    <string name="lable_tkip">TKIP</string>
    <string name="lable_aes">AES</string>

    <!-- Instructional strings -->
    <string-array name="explain_open_wifi">
        <item>&lt;b>Bottom line:&lt;/b> Don\'t do anything on this network that you wouldn\'t want someone else seeing.</item>
        <item>&lt;b>Explanation: &lt;/b>Open networks such as this have no security 
        	features enabled. This typically means that &lt;b>ALL DATA&lt;/b> is 
        	readable by anyone nearby.The exception is if you are visiting a web
			site or service that uses encryption. Web sites that use encryption
			will always have a URL which begins with \"https\" rather than \"http\".
			Services will vary by provider - if you are not certain that they use
			encryption, it is usually best to play it safe and wait until you are
			on a more secure network.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hotspot_(Wi-Fi)#Security_concerns</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="explain_wep">
        <item>&lt;b>Bottom line:&lt;/b> Proceed with caution! This network has minor protection that is easily broken.</item>
        <item>&lt;b>Explanation: &lt;/b> WEP is an older securtiy mechanism which 
            worked well when it was introduced over a decade ago. However, modern
            attacks against it have rendered it useless. You really should not consider
            </item>
        <item></item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wired_Equivalent_Privacy</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="explain_wps">
        <item>&lt;b>Bottom line:&lt;/b> You are probably safe, but be forewarned. This network can be rather easily hacked.</item>
        <item>&lt;b>Explanation: &lt;/b> WPS is a system which allows you to more easily
            connect devices to a wireless network. Properly implemented, this poses little
            threat. However, recent developments have allowed attackers to use this system
            to gain unauthorized access with relative ease. Though the attack is not yet
            commonplace - it\'s popularity is sure to grow.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wi-Fi_Protected_Setup</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="explain_wpa">
        <item>&lt;b>Bottom line:&lt;/b> This network uses an excellent form of security. It\'s only real weakness is an easy password - make sure it\'s a good one. </item>
        <item>&lt;b>Explanation: &lt;/b> WPA and WPA2 are considered the best form of wireless
            security. They are typically used with a shared password (one password per network).
            This means that the security is only as good as the password. Make sure it\'s hard
            to guess and that only the people who are allowed on the network know it.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wi-Fi_Protected_Access</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="explain_tkip">
        <item>&lt;b>Bottom line:&lt;/b> You are most likely perfectly safe. However, this network uses an older form of encryption which has several known vulnerabilities. </item>
        <item>&lt;b>Explanation: &lt;/b> TKIP is an older form of security which has similar
            attributes to the equally old WEP system. In fact, those attributes are so similar
            that it is vulnerable to the same types of attacks. In general, using TKIP should
            be avoided in favor of the newer AES or CCMP systems.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Temporal_Key_Integrity_Protocol</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="explain_aes">
        <item>&lt;b>Bottom line:&lt;/b> Excellent encryption! AES is quite literally the gold-standard for securing communications.</item>
        <item>&lt;b>Explanation: &lt;/b> AES is one of the strongest forms of security available.
            It is used in everything from encrypting wireless networks to protecting military
            and government secrets. There are no known direct attacks against AES. However, dumb
            luck and poor implementation can still provide back-doors for attackers. As with
            most things, you should trust but verify.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Advanced_Encryption_Standard</item>
    </string-array>
    
        <string name="summary_hint">Click any item for more information</string>
        <string name="detail_wikipedia">Find out more! (Wikipedia)</string>
        <string name="blue_lock">Blue combination lock</string>

</resources>