<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Wifi Security Check</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Wifi Security Check</string>
    <string name="main_button_start">Start Scan!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_summary">Scan Summary</string>

    <!-- Lables -->
    <string name="lable_security">Security:</string>
    <string name="lable_open_wifi">Open Wifi</string>
    <string name="lable_wep">WEP</string>
    <string name="lable_wps">WPS</string>
    <string name="lable_wpa">WPA</string>
    <string name="lable_wpa2">WPA2</string>
    <string name="lable_tkip">TKIP</string>
    <string name="lable_aes">AES</string>

    <!-- Instructional strings -->
    <string-array name="explain_open_wifi">
        <item>&lt;b>Bottom line:&lt;/b> Don\'t do anything on this network that you wouldn\'t want someone else seeing.</item>
        <item>&lt;b>Explanation: &lt;/b>Open networks such as this have no security 
        	features enabled. This typically means that &lt;b>ALL DATA&lt;/b> is 
        	readable by anyone nearby.The exception is if you are visiting a web
			site or service that uses encryption. Web sites that use encryption
			will always have a URL which begins with \"https\" rather than \"http\".
			Services will vary by provider - if you are not certain that they use
			encryption it is usually best to play it safe and wait until you are
			on a more secure network.</item>
        <item>This network is safe to use for:&lt;li>General web browsing (news, sports, games)&lt;/li>&lt;li>Viewing encrypted web sites (most email, facebook, etc.)&lt;/li></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="explain_wep">
        <item><b>Bottom line:</b> Proceed with caution! This network has minor protection that is easily broken.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="explain_wps">
        <item><b>Bottom line:</b> You are probably safe, but be forewarned. This network can be rather easily hacked.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="explain_wpa">
        <item><b>Bottom line:</b> This network uses an excellent form of security. It\'s only real weakness is an easy password - make sure it\'s a good one. </item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="explain_tkip">
        <item><b>Bottom line:</b> You are most likely perfectly safe. However, this network uses an older form of encryption which has several known vulnerabilities. </item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="explain_aes">
        <item><b>Bottom line:</b> Excellent encryption! AES is quite literally the gold-standard for securing communications.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_explanation">Further Explanation</string>

</resources>